[Blood River]
[Based on the novel of the same name from Zhou Munan's Youth in Jianghu series]
[Available on fanqienovel.com & bkneng.com]
[Episode 32]
You were hit by countless blow of my blade qi
in order to protect that lass.
You've sustained serious internal injuries.
If you utilize your arts within the next 15 minutes,
I don't even need to kill you.
You'll die from the severance of your nerves and meridians.
Mr. Su.
Second Master Tu.
Mr. Su,
stop calling me that.
You may call me Tu Wan.
You and I are friends.
Use this time to regulate your breathing.
I'll buy you some time.
15 minutes, huh?
I wish to give it a try.
Do you wish to save him?
Yes, I do.
I want to save him.
You think you can save him?
Judging from your cultivation stage,
I suppose you haven't reached the Vajra Mortal-Stage yet.
It seems I'm being belittled.
Since you can corner Mr. Su to this extent,
I suppose you're running out of strength as well.
Perhaps the current you
is weaker than a Vajra Mortal-Stage cultivator!
Since you have a death wish,
I shall grant your wish.
Stop!
Now, even a drugged puppet
is enough to corner me to this extent.
If they form an army with these puppets,
I'm sure Prince of Langya
will be no match for Yong.
It's just that this Night Crow is...
Perfect.
What a shame.
Ms. Night Crow, what are you lamenting about?
It's a shame that I can never create
another perfect drugged puppet like him.
The others
are inferior to him.
You'll find similar ones eventually.
After all, there are plenty of good prospects left
in Tianqi City.
Tonight is a good night
to reap some lives.
Tu Wan!
Just leave!
Mr. Su,
it hasn't even been
15 minutes yet.
You've done more than enough.
If this continues,
you'll die!
It's been some time
since I arrived at Tianqi City.
I've heard of your name before.
You're Second Master Tu of Thousand-Gold Tower.
So, are the people of Thousand-Gold Tower
also willing to risk their lives
for their friends' sake?
Who said I wouldn't risk my life for my friends
just because I'm Second Master Tu?
What if I'm Tu Wan, then?
Can I sacrifice myself for my friends, then?
When a man encounters a woman he fancies,
and, he can't forget about her after their first encounter,
we call that love at first sight.
But for men,
if we ever meet a man we can entrust ourselves to after our encounter,
we call that an instant bond.
Mr. Su and I
had an instant bond.
Excellent words.
Mr. Su,
I'm incompetent at martial arts.
This is the furthest I can go.
How could this be?
It hasn't even been
15 minutes yet.
It's because I'm Su Muyu.
I'm Su Muyu of Blood River.
Therefore, I'm always
stronger
than what people think of me.
Fine.
Initially, I wanted to visit a pleasure house.
But suddenly, I sensed
a strong killing intent coming from here.
Back then, I turned around and ran away.
I ran across three streets in a row.
In my mind, I was thinking
that I should come and take a look.
But in reality,
I was still terrified.
My fear suddenly went away
when he unsheathed his sword.
Perhaps I'll turn into someone
like Big Brother in the future.
Someone fat-headed and big-eared,
sly and deceitful.
But now,
I'm still Tu Wan.
I can sacrifice myself
for my friends.
Thank you so much.
I'll surely remember
your kindness today.
I'll take Miss Bai and treat her condition first.
I'll entrust this place to you.
Go ahead. Don't worry.
It seems this ancient manual
is related
to the puppet spell somehow.
The puppet spell
is now in the grasp of Medicine King Valley.
If I can receive the help of Medicine King,
perhaps I can catch a glimpse of its secrets.
Come in.
Ms. Yun.
I instructed you to infiltrate the ranks of
the deputy commander's Jinwu Guards.
But now, you're paying me a visit.
Has the deputy commander's son's illness
shown signs of improvement?
Second Master Tu of Thousand-Gold Tower
brought a healer here.
The deputy commander
wanted her to stay.
But one of their friends suddenly came here
and took them away.
What happened after that?
What happened after they left
the deputy commander's manor?
After they left the deputy commander's manor,
they encountered an assassin.
Who was the assassin?
The assassin wielded six blades.
Was it Xu Liuyun, the Blade Ghost of Nanjue?
Indeed.
I didn't dare to get near them.
I merely observed the encounter from afar.
It seemed like the healer was injured.
I think she was
the assassin's true target
from the start.
So, his friend was able to kill the Blade Ghost.
And, the healer was targeted by
the Blade Ghost.
You said Second Master Tu
hired them to provide treatment, right?
Which clinic do they come from?
He-Yu Clinic of Mingcheng Alley.
I understand now.
I finished off
your Wolf.
How come your Tiger
can finish off my Wolf?
Isn't it common for tigers
to prey on wolves?
Wolves come in packs.
Tigers are solitary beasts.
As the saying goes, two fists cannot stand against four hands.
Your tiger is alone.
It's no match for my pack of wolves.
Where's your pack of wolves, then?
Over here.
This...
Are you sure about this?
Can't I do so?
I'm dead.
Why isn't Master back yet?
Don't worry.
Master Su is there.
Even if it's the deputy commander's manor,
he can still enter and exit at will.
Enough.
If you're still worried about them,
I'll perform divination for you.
By divination, you meant tossing a coin.
Is it even accurate?
It had always worked.
Su Muyu hasn't returned yet.
Why aren't you panicking at all?
I remember that someone was panicking
when
we were in Tianqi City.
Times have changed.
Yu is amazing.
I don't think he needs
a useless and harmless person like me to worry about him.
I think
we should be worried about
the deputy commander instead.
Wait.
Was that another joke?
What if
I were there instead of Mr. Su?
Would you worry about me?
I mean,
I'm the current head of the family.
If only I could use my Poison-Sand Palm now.
I would've killed you in an instant.
You think
you're a worthy head of family?
This is bad.
Master.
Xu Liuyun is dead.
How could that be?
Isn't he the Blade Ghost?
Even so, he's a human.
He's not unkillable.
General Dian,
your uncle,
hired him to assassinate the miracle physician
of Medicine King Valley.
He was inferior to Umbrella Ghost.
He was killed off instead.
I suppose
he's panicking right now.
He'll surely mobilize
more of his hidden blades in the dark.
I don't need to worry
if it's Uncle we're talking about.
Yong.
Are you not worried
due to the fact
that he's your uncle?
Or are you not worried
due to his capabilities?
Now,
you're already better than me.
You wish to get something done,
but you don't want to dirty your hands.
I suppose kinship
is an excellent tool indeed.
Let's see
if Uncle can get things done
in a beautiful manner.
If not,
we have no choice but to depend on Su Changhe.
He's
a double-edged sword.
Her bleeding has been stopped.
Yu,
did you use
the Unyielding Gold on Master?
I think so.
Miss Bai instructed me to do so.
But she fainted
before I managed to do it.
You did great.
Without it,
I suppose
no one could save her.
Master was struck by blades.
The blade qi
is still within her body.
We have to force it out of her.
Head of Mu family.
Yes.
Listen to my command.
When I give you the signal,
strike Master's Baihui acupoint
with your palm.
Don't use too much force.
Make sure it's gentle yet strong at the same time.
If not,
even if Master does survive,
her skull will be dented.
She'll be furious.
I understand.
This is my expertise.
Zhaoyan,
what do I need to do?
Yu,
you don't need to do anything for now.
You were seriously wounded as well.
You should rest and recuperate.
Okay.
Just focus on saving her.
You may ignore me.
Yu.
What happened?
When Miss Bai went out to give diagnoses,
she realized
that some noblemen were struck by the puppet poison.
She was ambushed on her way back.
She was seriously wounded.
I failed to protect Miss Bai.
Could the assailant be
Xu Liuyun?
How did you know?
This morning, I received news
that Xu Liuyun, the Blade Ghost, had entered Tianqi City.
And, he even made contact with Flying Tiger General's Residence.
I didn't expect him
to act this quickly.
Did he escape?
He's already dead.
The culprit was Flying Tiger General.
It seems Changhe's initial speculation was spot-on.
This was the work of Xiao Yong, the first prince.
And, that Night Crow,
it's likely that she's hiding in Flying Tiger General's Residence.
We kept a close eye on their residence
in order to track down Night Crow.
However,
they always tried to throw us off with tricks,
causing us to expend a lot of energy to track them down.
In the end, it was a ruse.
It seems the Blade Ghost
left the residence
when we were tricked by the feint attack.
I need to head there.
Yu,
have you lost your mind?
Just ignore me.
Keep guard over the place.
Yu, you mustn't.
Your current priority
is to rest and recuperate.
If you seek revenge
in this state,
you'll lose more than you'll gain.
What do you think will happen next
if I don't head there
right now?
Do you think He-Yu Clinic will still be safe?
If I were them, and I found out
that Miss Bai has figured out the secret behind the drugged puppets,
I would get rid of her
at all costs.
Even if the Blade Ghost is dead,
I'll send out the rest of my elite members
to hunt her down.
It seems a group of elites
will gather at this clinic soon.
Some of the arrays set up by
Qingyang and I are still active.
It shouldn't be that easy for outsiders to enter this place.
What if we shift Miss Bai elsewhere?
What if we shift her to the secret chamber where Changhe is meditating?
Although I know nothing about medicine,
there are similarities between the arts of poison and the arts of medicine.
We can't afford to move her around now.
If we do,
her zhenqi will react wildly.
And, she might die at any time.
That's why I have to go.
I have to show them
my rage.
I understand now.
You're trying to tell them
that Miss Bai is dead.
That's why you're so enraged
that you're forsaking your life.
Fine.
Yu,
I'll join you.
Stay here and protect everyone.
But Yu...
Changhe is still on a reclusive retreat.
We have to depend on you.
All right.
Xuewei and I will remain here.
Yu, you don't need to worry.
Take care.
They're here.
[Tranquil Delight]
All of you, stand back!
Is this
an array?
Evil spirits.
These are mere tricks.
I'll dispel it.
So, it's you.
I did think about who my inner demon would be.
It could've been Yi Bu, who dictated our lives for many years.
Or my grandfather, who constantly lectured
and disciplined me.
Perhaps it could've been myself as well.
But I never expected it
to be you.
Su Muyu,
perhaps I envied your straightforward
and carefree spirit all this while.
But this time,
as my inner demon,
I get to face you again.
This time,
I won't back off.
Qingyang and I
had set up the Myriad Fantasy Array outside.
Those who enter the array will be trapped there,
and their inner demon will be shown.
But I'll set up
another poison array around the courtyard just in case.
All right.
We're reaching the crucial moment.
We can't afford to let anyone interrupt the process.
Understood.
I'll make sure
no one will interrupt us.
Xuewei,
your inner force is the gentlest among us.
Head inside
and expel the blade qi from Miss Bai's body.
Yumo and I will keep guard here.
All right.
The array has been dispelled.
Xie,
you're extraordinary indeed.
But there's one more poison array within.
I do not excel at the arts of poison.
Night Crow, please do something about it.
An array within an array, huh?
The poisonous miasma in the courtyard is pretty strong.
We shouldn't let it go to waste.
Go now.
He's absorbing Xuewei's poisonous miasma.
I don't care if you're his senior brother or not.
If you dare to step into the house,
I will kill you.
So,
this is the person
who absorbed Xuewei's poison.
Night Crow created this Gold-Body Puppet
and made him absorb Xuewei's poison.
He's Tang Lianyue's senior brother
and the deputy sect leader of Tang Clan,
Tang Linghuang.
So,
not only does he possess
Xuewei's arts of poison,
but he's also a Heaven-level master, huh?
That's right.
He's troublesome to deal with.
General!
This is bad!
Someone has infiltrated our residence!
Who?
It's me!
Su Muyu of Blood River,
how dare you?
What are you doing here?
Blood River invited Miss Bai
to Tianqi as our guest.
To us,
she's our dearest friend.
I once told her
that I would ensure her safety
as long as I was around.
But now, she's dead.
She was killed by the assassin
you hired.
I want you to give me an account.
Why should I?
This is your choice.
And I will make my choice now.
Do you know what kind of offense it is
to kill a general in Beili?
You will die by a thousand cuts,
and three generations of your kin will be executed.
Three generations of my kin, huh?
Su Muyu,
you're seriously wounded.
If you utilize your sword energy now,
you'll die for sure.
Even if you win, it'll be a Pyrrhic victory.
You'd better think twice.
Don't be reckless.
Don't be reckless?
This is the first time anyone has said that to me.
But this time,
I feel like being reckless!
The poisonous miasma has been completely absorbed.
Aren't you going to head inside?
Let me try out the power of the enhanced drugged puppet.
Su Muyu has infiltrated the general's residence.
The situation is dire.
Everyone,
please head back immediately.
Su Muyu isn't here?
He went to the general's residence instead?
But why?
He said General killed the miracle physician.
He went there to avenge her out of spite.
But judging from his state,
I suppose he has lost his mind.
We've already dispatched the Jinwu Guards
to the residence as reinforcements.
Did he actually say
that Bai Hehuai was dead?
She's surely dead.
Su Muyu was seriously wounded
when he infiltrated the residence.
However,
from the way he was swinging his sword,
I think he was trying to fight with reckless abandon.
If you guys don't head there,
I'm afraid
he'll massacre the entire residence.
Yu,
could it be
that we're going to die here?
Let's head back!
Stop!
Fine, then.
Who would've expected
both of us
to almost die from Xuewei's poison.
It seems Yu
created a commotion that was huge enough.
That's why they were lured back.
Are you guys okay?
This poison is...
Take this.
Don't worry.
I'll be fine.
How's Miss Bai doing?
Miss Bai is safe now.
Great.
I finally understand
why Yi Bu and the rest
would regard
a martial arts organization this highly.
One can catch a glimpse
of Blood River's formidable power
on Master Su alone.
It makes those of us
who barely survived the battlefield
seem all the more insignificant.
General, you once slew your enemies
on the battlefield valiantly
with your battle axes.
But now, you're manipulating people
and plotting sinister plots in Tianqi City.
Do you even remember
who you once were?
Xie Zaiye.
Master Su.
You're truly disappointing.
It seems Changhe was right back then.
Sometimes,
we should uproot everything
without leaving a single one behind.
I'm very impressed
by the courage you and Patriarch possessed.
I also regret the fact
that I'm not as courageous or capable as you two.
But this is my own choice.
Indeed.
It's because Changhe and I are strong enough.
That's why we can
get rid of the weeds
that are growing again.
It's been some time
since our last battle.
It seems
your inner force has improved considerably.
However, it's not as if my progress remained stagnant.
Tang Linghuang.
Your zhenqi is leaking everywhere,
your sword aura is intact,
and your killing intent has gotten stronger.
Master Su,
it seems you've gone demonic.
Looks like my martial aunt
is someone special to you.
Night Crow.
I will kill you.
You think you can kill me in that state?
You just took Tang Linghuang's attack head-on.
Now, we don't need to do anything.
You'll die from the poison
within 7-8 minutes.
But you're Su Muyu after all.
You overthrew both Blood River and Shadow Sect.
Who knows what will happen
if we let you leave?
So,
it's time for you to die here.
It's my first time seeing you in this state,
young Muyu.
Master.
Where's young Changhe?
If he sees you
in this pathetic state,
he'll surely mock you first.
After that,
he'll kill all of them.
Who are you?
Night Crow, the ghost physician.
A traitor of Medicine King Valley.
You were bold enough to turn
the future leader of the Tang Clan into a drugged puppet.
Now that you've offended them,
you won't get away easily.
Kill them!
Hell Palm?
Should we go after them?
No need for that.
Even if we do catch up to them,
she'll kill all of you.
Young Muyu, look at
how pathetic you look.
Fake diviner of the Mu family,
since you're here,
you should stop hiding.
Who are you?
You are...
It's me.
Long time no see, Mu Qingyang.
Have you been to Mount Wangcheng
and visited the sword deity you admired?
Aren't you the owner of the library,
Su Yunxiu?
[Su Yunxiu, Blood River]
I thought you were dead.
I merely left Blood River.
They couldn't track me down.
They had no choice but to say that I was dead.
I'm Su Yunxiu, you know?
I taught
both Su Muyu and Su Changhe.
It's impossible for me to die that easily.
Why do you still
look the same?
Yeah.
I wonder
why I still look the same.
Su Muyu!
You're here.
How's Miss Bai?
Miss Bai is fine.
I'm here to fetch you back.
This is great.
Young Muyu,
your teacher is still alive.
I'm standing right in front of you.
Why didn't you exhibit
any signs of joy at all?
Master, they said you were dead.
Changhe and I investigated the area after that.
We were 90% confident
that you had escaped.
What about the last 10%?
For the last 10%,
it was likely that you changed your identity
and joined Blood River again.
You do live up to your name as my disciple.
But young Muyu,
this is my first time seeing you
this hot-headed.
Why did you do so?
A good friend of ours,
the miracle physician, Bai Hehuai,
was seriously wounded by our foes
after she figured out their secrets.
And,
they wanted to silence her.
Su Muyu was seriously wounded as well
when he rescued her.
And now,
Miss Bai needs to rest and recuperate in a safe environment.
Therefore, Su Muyu
pretended that Miss Bai was dead
and that he wanted to seek revenge.
Only then would we be able to lure them away.
He pretended to be enraged?
To me, you were
obviously enraged.
Master, you're right.
I wasn't pretending.
That wasn't enough.
Not yet.
Was my rage not enough?
No.
The reason you gave us isn't convincing enough.
You
fancy her, don't you?
Indeed.
I fancy her.
This is great.
Why do you say so?
It's because someone finally made
Su Muyu fall in love.
That's great.
Su Muyu,
I'm happy to see your current state.
Although you're in a pathetic state now,
this is
the most handsome you
I've ever seen.
Do you know what an iceberg becomes
when it melts?
Master,
please stop teasing me.
It becomes the roaring ocean, silly boy.
All right now.
I'm going to leave.
I was just passing by Tianqi City.
I didn't expect
to witness such an interesting turn of events.
I know
that you could've left the residence by yourself.
You still have your trump card.
But you and young Changhe
are trying to create
a new Blood River after all.
If so, there's no room
for any error.
Su Muyu!
Let's go.
What exactly went wrong?
Why can't I break my limit and reach the ninth level?
What is it?
Changhe,
we received a message from Flying Tiger General's Residence.
They asked you when you would finish your retreat.
Why are they so impatient?
I'll do it when the time is right.
Last night,
something happened at Flying Tiger General's Residence.
What happened?
Firstly, Miss Bai
found out about their secrets.
Due to that, she was seriously wounded.
After that, in order to lure their foes away,
Yu disregarded the wounds that he had sustained
and attacked Flying Tiger General's Residence forcefully.
Yu almost
wiped all of them out.
They only managed to drive back Yu
after their reinforcements arrived.
Now, both Yu and Miss Bai
are seriously wounded.
They're hiding
in a remote house as we speak.
Have Dian Ye and his men lost their minds?
I said that I could help them.
But under no circumstances
are our Blood River members to be harmed.
Changhe,
why must we work with them?
If we had stepped in
in time last night,
Yu might not
have been hurt that badly.
Are you questioning me?
♪Like fate, winding with the tide♪
♪Who can ford this river of night?♪
♪Where's the far shore we chase all our lives?♪
♪Surrendering all hues for a glimmer of light♪
♪Through joy and sorrow♪
♪Still I can't let go♪
♪Longing keeps me awake at night♪
♪My heart no longer my own♪
♪No one can escape from love♪
♪How many hidden feelings♪
♪Sink in silence deep?♪
♪Searching through the endless nights♪
♪Struggling on the edge of love and pain♪
♪Shadows crossing shadows♪
♪Whose name hides in your eyes?♪
♪When the wind blows, ask not when I shall return♪
♪Ask not when I shall return♪
♪Like fate, winding with the tide♪
♪Who can ford this river of night?♪
♪Where's the far shore we chase all our lives?♪
♪Surrendering all hues for a glimmer of light♪
♪Through joy and sorrow♪
♪Still I can't let go♪
♪Longing keeps me awake at night♪
♪My heart no longer my own♪
♪No one can escape from love♪